Narrator: 1
Announcer: The train waiting on platform thirteen is the nine forty-eight Great Western train to Oxford,
calling at Slough, Reading, Didcot Parkway, and Oxford.
A: That’s our train. Platform thirteen. Come on.
B: OK. Let’s go.
Narrator: 2
A: Excuse me! How far is it to Dublin?
B: It’s about forty kilometres.
A: Thanks a lot.
Narrator: 3
A: Just one more game. Come on!
B: Fifteen–love.
A: Fantastic serve!
Narrator: 4
A: Will all passengers on flight B-A two three four to Budapest
please go to Gate sixty immediately.
B: Gate sixty. Is that our flight?
C: No, it’s to Budapest, not Bucharest.
Narrator: 5
A: How much is that?
B: Two pizzas and a Coke. That’s seventeen pounds.
Narrator: 6
A: What’s your address?
B: It’s eighty Park Road.
A: Sorry?
B: Eighty, eight-oh. Park Road.
Narrator: 7
A: OK, can you be quiet, please? Open your books on page ninety.
B: What page is it?
C: Page ninety.